let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Geb\u00e4ude", "answer": "buildings", "options": ["Suit, Costume", "Operation,", "buildings", "process"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Ablauf", "answer": "expired", "options": ["Leadership, Conduct", "expired", "Triangle", "Crucial"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Leitung", "answer": "Leadership, Conduct", "options": ["Leadership, Conduct", "Crucial", "Suit, Costume", "process"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "bedinungen", "answer": "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "options": ["term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Task", "circle"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "H\u00e4ufig", "answer": "Frequently", "options": ["Operation,", "Script", "Frequently", "Talent"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "Operation,", "options": ["Operation,", "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "expired"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "Seitew\u00e4rts", "answer": "Sideways", "options": ["Sideways", "Assumption", "buildings", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "answer": "Backward", "options": ["Crucial", "circle", "process", "Backward"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Angabe", "answer": "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "options": ["circle", "Script", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "expired"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Vierecke", "answer": "Rectangular", "options": ["Task", "circle", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Rectangular"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Aufgabe", "answer": "Task", "options": ["Task", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "Wastage", "buildings"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "kreis", "answer": "circle", "options": ["circle", "Judgement", "Rectangular", "Suit, Costume"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Wesentlich", "answer": "Crucial", "options": ["Task", "Crucial", "Rectangular", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Vorw\u00e4rts", "answer": "forward", "options": ["forward", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "Backward", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Gewitter", "answer": "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "options": ["Crucial", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "Script"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "knapp", "answer": "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "options": ["almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "Task", "Contract", "process"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Verlauf", "answer": "process", "options": ["process", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "circle", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Behalter", "answer": "Container", "options": ["buildings", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "Crucial", "Container"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Dreieck", "answer": "Triangle", "options": ["Triangle", "Judgement", "Wastage", "Operation,"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Urteil", "answer": "Judgement", "options": ["Judgement", "Backward", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "expired"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Gabe", "answer": "Talent", "options": ["Crucial", "Wastage", "Talent", "Script"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Schrifft", "answer": "Script", "options": ["expired", "Script", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "Talent"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Hinweise", "answer": "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "options": ["Frequently", "circle", "process", "trip, Clue, Sulivu"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Abfall", "answer": "Wastage", "options": ["Container", "Wastage", "Backward", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Vertrag", "answer": "Contract", "options": ["Contract", "Sideways", "Leadership, Conduct", "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Ahnung", "answer": "Assumption", "options": ["Backward", "Assumption", "Frequently", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Anzug", "answer": "Suit, Costume", "options": ["Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "Contract", "Suit, Costume", "Backward"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Mangel", "answer": "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "options": ["Assumption", "Contract", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "Talent"]}];